Filene Co-operative Association Publications, Copies of ECHO 5566 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Filene Co-operative Association Publications, Copies of ECHO
1902-1912
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Filene Co-operative Association
5566 PUBS
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Publications (documents).
Publication of the Filene Co-Operative Association, 1902-1912
5664265
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, April 17, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, June 05, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Echo was a publication of the Filene Co-Operative Association, the company union of the William Filene's Sons Company, an American department store in Boston, Massachusetts.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of issues of Echo, the publication of the Filene Co-Operative Association, 1902-1912. It includes 48 single copies of Echo and 1 bound copy.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Retail trade -- Employees; Filene Co-Operative Association
5664265
- Echo, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Echo (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    By Charles H. Eastman. v.1:no.4 (1902:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Echo (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By Charles H. Eastman. v.1:no.5 (1902:Dec.). Item is in English.
- Echo, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Echo (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Charles H. Eastman. v.1:no.6 (1903:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Echo (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Charles H. Eastman. v.1:no.7 (1903:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Echo (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Charles H. Eastman. v.1:no.8 (1903:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Charles H. Eastman. v.1:no.10 (1903:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By H. B. Scates. v.1:no.11 (1903:June). Item is in English.
- Echo, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By G. R. Brigham. v.4:no.1 (1906:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 3)
    v.4:no.5 (1906:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 3)
    v.4:no.6 (1906:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By D. Bartholomew. v.4:no.7 (1906:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By D. Bartholomew. v.4:no.8 (1906:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By D. Bartholomew. v.4:no.9 (1906:Dec.). Item is in English.
- Echo, 1907 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 4)
    v.4:no.10 (1907:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By D. Bartholomew. v.4:no.11 (1907:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 4)
    v.5:no.1 (1907:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 4)
    v.5:no.3 (1907:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 4)
    v.5:no.4 (1907:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 4)
    v.5:no.5 (1907:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 4)
    v.5:no.6 (1907:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 4)
    v.5:no.7 (1907:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 4)
    v.5:no.8 (1907:Dec.). Item is in English.
- Echo, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By G. G. Goldie. v.5:no.9 (1908:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By G. G. Goldie. v.5:no.10 (1908:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By G. G. Goldie. v.5:no.11 (1908:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By G. G. Goldie. v.5:no.12 (1908:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By George M. Watson. v.6:no.2 (1908:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By George M. Watson. v.6:no.3 (1908:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By George M. Watson. v.6:no.4 (1908:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By George M. Watson. v.6:no.5 (1908:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By George M. Watson. v.6:no.6 (1908:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By George M. Watson. v.6:no.7 (1908:Nov.). Item is in English.
- Echo, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By John F. King. v.6:no.9 (1909:Jan.). Success Number. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By John F. King. v.6:no.10 (1909:Feb.). What Is The Matter With The F.C.A?. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By John F. King. v.6:no.11 (1909:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By John F. King. v.6:no.12 (1909:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By William H. McLeod. v.6:no.13 (1909:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By William H. McLeod. v.6:no.14 (1909:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By William H. McLeod. v.6:no.15 (1909:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By William H. McLeod. v.6:no.16 (1909:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By William H. McLeod. v.6:no.17 (1909:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By William H. McLeod. v.6:no.18 (1909:Oct.). Exposition Number: Tenth Anniversary of the Filene Co-operative Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Bernard F. Tully. v.7:no.7 (1909:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Bernard F. Tully. v.7:no.8 (1909:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Bernard F. Tully. v.7:no.9 (1910:Jan.). Item is in English.
- Echo, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Bernard F. Tully. v.7:no.10 (1910:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Bernard F. Tully. v.7:no.11 (1910:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Bernard F. Tully. v.8:no.1 (1910:May). Item is in English.
- Echo, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Louis E. Schleber. v.8:no.12 (1911:Apr.) - v.9:no.11 (1912:Mar.). Signed by Louis E. Schleber, Louis T. McMahon, and Franklin M. Spear. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The F. C. A. Echo (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Louis E. Schleber. v.8:no.12 (1911:Apr.). Item is in English.
- Echo, 1911-1912; Bound volume (Box 1, Folder 9)